Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - Administrative Papers 1969-1970
    - COSEP - Funds., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      Winkelman, Donald M.; Rogers, Thomas R. IBM.
    - CO8EP - Funds. Jones, William D.; Lee, Gary A.; Morse, Chandler. Cornell University-Hampton Institute Exchange Program; IBM., 1970-71 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - COSEP - Proposal for a Division of Educational Opportunity., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      Johnson, Houston; Plane, Robert A.; Williams, L. Pearce; Kahn, Alfred E.; Knapp, David C.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      Articles pertaining to Black studies and race issues.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1969-70 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center. Kennedy, W. Keith; Joseph, Gloria I.; Clarke, John H. Black student recruitment; Black Liberation Front; Wake Forest University; Rockefeller Brothers Fund., 1969-70 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center. Turner, James E.; Kearse, Lee A.; Brenes, Dalai; Plane, Robert A.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Wari House Cooperative; 310 Triphammer Road; Security., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      Turner, James E. Wari House Cooperative; Security.
    - Urban Development Corporation. Greater Ithaca Community Advisory Committee; Housing., 1969-70 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Urban Development Corporation., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      Carlson, Scott. New York State Urban Development Corporation; Housing.
    - Office of the Registrar. Jackson, R. Peter., 1970-71 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Office of the Registrar. Jackson, R. Peter., 1971 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - University Advisory Committee on Undergraduate Education. Plane, Robert A.; Scott, Robert A. Each In His Own Time by Scott; Educational reform., 1970-71 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Society for the Humanities., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      Guerlac, Henry; Black, Max; Kammen, Michael G.; Eddy, Donald D.; Stevens, Stoddard M. Andrew W. Mellon Foundation.
    - Society for the Humanities., 1970-71 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      Guerlac, Henry; Black, Max; Seznec, Jean; Bloom, Harold. Seeley G. Mudd Fund; Andrew W. Mellon Foundation.
    - Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1966-67 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      Smith, William A.; Sampson, Martin W.; Smith, Julian C.
    - Vice Provost., 1967-70 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      Kennedy, W. Keith. Rockefeller Foundation; Merce Cunningham Dance Group; SUNY relations with Cornell University.
    - Vice Provost., 1965-71 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      Palm, Charles E.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Swallow, William H. SUNY tuition; SUNY relations with Cornell University.
    - Academic Appointments., 1969-70 (Box 33, Folder 34)
      Plane, Robert A.
    - Division of Biological Sciences. Steward, F. C.; Morison, Robert S.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Lawrence, Samuel A. Alexander Professorship; Ten year projection for the Division; Computers., 1965-71 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1968-71 (Box 33, Folder 36)
      Palm, Charles E.; O'Brien, Richard D. Mote Marine Laboratory; National Institutes of Health; Isles of Shoals Project.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 37)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Palm, Charles E.; Fuchs, Wolfgang H. J.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Hall, Jackson O.; Morison, Robert S.; Borgmann, Carl W. Cornell Daily Sun; Ford Foundation.
    - Division of Biological Sciences - Long Term Support. Kennedy, W. Keith; Plane, Robert A.; Morison, Robert S.; Capranica, R. R.; Wallace, Bruce., 1966-70 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1963-65 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Arthur A. Alien Award.
    - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Spofford, Sally Hoyt.
    - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1966-70 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Kennedy, W. Keith; Pettingill, Olin Sewall. University Publications.
    - Cornell University - Mote Marine Laboratory., 1968-71 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Gilbert, Perry W.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced studies., 1967-68 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Long, Franklin A.; Rathjens, George W. Salaries for scientists; Ford Foundation.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1968 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Long, Franklin A.; Rathjens, George W.; Mote, W. R.
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies. Long, Franklin A.; Rathjens, George W.; Perkins, James A. New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority; United States Dept, of Defense; Scientists and Social Responsibility (Conference)., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder S)
    - Vice President for Research and Advanced Studies., 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Long, Franklin A.; Leurgans, Paul J.; Cooke, W. Donald; Rathjens, George W.; Perkins, James A. Government funding agencies.
    - Center for Applied Mathematics., 1966-71 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Payne, Lawrence E.; Sears, William R.
    - Materials Science Center., 1969-71 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Hannay, Bruce; Nowick, A. S.; Owen, Walter S. Xerox Corporation; MSC Executive Committee.
    - Materials Science Center - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes., 1968-71 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research. Sagan, Carl; Payne, John D.; Gold, Thomas; Kahn, Alfred E.; Cooke, W. Donald; Littel, Edward G. Security of lunar sample., 1967-70 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      Drake, Frank D.; York, Carl M.; Hunt, Daniel. National Science Foundation, Office of National Centers and Facilities Operations.
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo ionospheric Observatory., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      Owen, Thomas; Gold, Thomas; Hunt, Daniel. National Science Foundation; Political and personal conditions at AIO.
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      Owen, Thomas; Gold, Thomas; Hunt, Daniel. National Science Foundation; Political and personal conditions at AIO; Cornell University - National Science Foundation relations.
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Plane, Robert A.; Gold, Thomas.
    - Cornell University Libraries. Healey, George H.; Barlow, Mark; Brown, Stuart M.; Korman, Gerd; Miller, J. Gormly; Finch, C. Herbert. Syracuse University - Cornell University Joint Special Collections Library (New York Special Collections Research Center); Copyright/media problems; Fines; Center for Research Libraries., 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      Wilson, Logan; Catlin, George E. B.; Kaser, David. Association of Research Libraries; Center for Research Libraries; Five Associated University Libraries; Special Collections Library.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      Kaser, David; Gates, Paul W. Cornell University Library Staff Association.
    - Cornell University Libraries. Center for Research Libraries., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Office of Sponsored Research., 1967-69 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      Rogers, Thomas R. Interdisciplinary Center of Regional Studies (Proposed).
    - Office of Sponsored Research. Rogers, Thomas R.; Chappie, Elliot D.; Curtiss, Peter A.; Levin, Louis. National Science Foundation., 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Office of Sponsored Research., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      Rogers, Thomas R.; Novak, Joseph D. Shell Merit Fellowship Program; National Science Foundation.
    - Research - Dept, of Defense., 1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      Handler, Philip. National Academy of Sciences.
    - Research - Miscellaneous., 1965-67 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      Rogers, Thomas R.; Long, Franklin A. Classified research; Advanced Research Projects Agency.
    - Research - Miscellaneous., 1968-71 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      Hastie, John W. National Science Foundation; Classified research.
    - Cornell Research Board., 1963-70 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      Plane, Robert A.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Rolley, William C.; Long, Franklin A.; Mackesey, Thomas W.
    - Vice President for Social and Environmental Studies. Carter, Lisle C.; Hasler, Arthur; Knapp, David C.; Davidson, H. Justin. New York City Urban Fellowship Program., 1969-71 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Center for Housing and Environmental Studies., 1963-68 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      Beyer, Glenn H.; Loberg, Harry J.
    - Environmental Health Committee. Moore, Norman S.; Blomquist, Alfred T.; Winding, Charles C. Pesticide storage; Chemical Hazards Committee., 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Center for Environmental Quality Management., 1965-69 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      Lynn, Walter R.; Whitlock, John H.; Schultz, Andrew S. Ford Foundation; Chemical Hazards Committee; Dept, of Environmental Systems Engineering (in College of Engineering, Proposed).
    - Center for International Studies., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      Plane, Robert A.; Muller, Steven; Esman, Milton J.; Marden, Parker G.; Revelle, Roger. International Population Program; Peace Studies Program; Ford Foundation; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - Center for International Studies. Gair, James W.; Carter, Lisle C.; Esman, Milton J.; Plane, Robert A.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Clark, Hays. American Council on Education; Ivy League Consultative Group; Committee on Soviet Studies; National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, International Programs Office; Southeast Asia Program., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Center for Quantitative Economics. Mellor, John W.; Gross, James A.; Brown, Stuart M.; Liu, Ta-Chung; Smidt, Seymour., 1968-69 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Center for Quantitative Economics. Carter, Lisle C.; Dhrymes, Phoebus J.; Knapp, David C.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Liu, Ta-Chung; Clemhout, Simone; Mellor, John W.; Christ, Carl F. National Science Foundation., 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Center for Quantitative Economics. Liu, Ta-Chung. Study Committee in Economics; Committee on New Directions in the Social Sciences (Hildebrand); National Science Foundation., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Center for Quantitative Economics. Carter, Lisle C.; Plane, Robert A.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Liu, Ta-Chung; Nerlove, Marc; Perkins, James A.; Davis, Tom E. University-wide centers., 1968-71 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Center for Research in Education. Rogers, Thomas R.; Ginsburg, Herbert; Camhi, Jane; Esman, Milton J.; Ford, Boyce L.; Tobias, Sheila; Baldwin, Alfred L.; Hilton, Peter J.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Reading and Writing Program (Proposed); Female Studies Program; Center for International Studies; Ithaca (NY) Alternate Junior High School., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center., 1966-70 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      Dworsky, Leonard B.; Robison, Howard W.
    - Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center., 1970-71 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      Dworsky, Leonard B.
    - Center for Urban Development and Research., 1968-70 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Winston, Oliver C.; Talbot, Allan R.; Logue, Edward J.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Dept, of City and Regional Planning; New York State Urban Development Corporation; New York State Redevelopment Corporation.
    - Center for Urban Development and Research., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Jones, Barclay G.; Whyte, William Foote. Urban Affairs Center.
    - Center for Urban Development and Research., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Reissman, Leonard; Winston, Oliver C. Ford Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      Whyte, William Foote; Eagle, Vernon; Nichols, Benjamin. Office of Sponsored Research; Ford Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Whyte, William Foote; Nichols, Benjamin; Saltford, Richard A.; Bard, Bruce H.; Carter, Lisle C.; Stamp, Neal R.; Abbott, Edward P. Ford Foundation; Economic Opportunity Corporation of Tompkins County; Cornell Campus Coalition.
    - Human Affairs Program. Carter, Lisle C.; Nichols, Benjamin. Storefront Project., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Psychology Coordinating Committee. Carter, Lisle C.; Nichols, Benjamin., 1969-70 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Science and Technology., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Long, Franklin A.; Black, Max; Brady, Nyle C. Cornell University Program on Science, Technology and Society; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
    - Science and Technology., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      Morison, Robert S.; McDermott, Walsh; Long, Franklin A.; Black, Max; Kahn, Alfred E.; Bowers, Raymond. Program on Science, Technology and Society.
    - Cornell University Press., 1958-71 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Kerns, M. R.; Arden, Kelvin J.; Howley, Roger; Sproull, Robert L. University Publications.
    - Cornell University Press - Board of Editors., 1965-69 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - University Publications., 1967-71 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Vice President - Business., 1959-70 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      Burton, John E. New York State Dormitory Authority; New York Telephone Company; Housing.
    - Vice President for Administration., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Kiplinger, Austin H.
    - Vice President for Administration. Lawrence, Samuel A.; Kershaw, Joseph A.; Davidson, H. Justin. McKinsey Study Plan., 1969-70 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Vice President for Administration. Lawrence, Samuel A.; Plane, Robert A.; Vaughan, Henry G.; Ahearne, John F. Housing and dining., 1969-71 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Vice President for Administration - Budget., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.
    - Building and Maintenance Costs., 1966-70 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Dept, of Buildings and Properties., 1965-70 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      Lawrence, Samuel A. Board of Trustees - Buildings and Properties Committee.
    - Dept, of Buildings and Properties., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      Desch, Noel.
    - Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid. Barlow, Mark; Anderson, Jon T.; McCalmon, Byron G. McMullen Fund; Shell Companies Foundation; Shell Merit Programs; John F. Kennedy Memorial Award., 1966-69 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid. Anderson, Jon T. United States Rubber Company; Seven Universities Group., 1966-70 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid., 1969-71 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      Anderson, Jon T.; Cornell, Candace.
    - Consolidation of Student Loan Procedures and Check Cashing., 1967-68 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      Barlow, Mark; Lee, Gary A.; Durland, Lewis H.; Miller, Ralph.
    - Travel Office., 1967-71 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - General Services., 1968-71 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      Rogers, Walter B.
    - Personnel Department, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      Willers, Diedrich K. Labor relations.
    - Personnel Department, 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Barnette, Thomas W. Unions; United States Office for Civil Rights.
    - Personnel Department, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      Willers, Diedrich K. United States Office for Civil Rights; Affirmative action.
    - Affirmative Action., 1969-70 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      Dunston, James M.; Hall, Jackson O. TOMPCO Better Housing, Inc.; Minority group employment; Social Sciences Building; Affirmative Action Program; Yale University; University of Chicago.
    - Affirmative Action., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Plane, Robert A. Affirmative Action Program; Black faculty; Deans' responses to query regarding black faculty.
    - Affirmative Action., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Cooke, W. Donald; Peterson, Arthur H.; Leahy, Joseph F.; Plane, Robert A.; Brady, Nyle C. Affirmative Action Program; Equal Opportunity Program; Women's rights; United States Office for Civil Rights; Quotas; Black faculty; Wesleyan University; Minority faculty.
    - Affirmative Action., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      Plane, Robert A.; Willers, Diedrich K.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Leahy, Joseph F.; Lawrence, Samuel A. United States Office for Civil Rights; Affirmative Action Program.
    - Affirmative Action - Campus Construction., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      Tobin, Thomas L.; Dunston, James M.; Jacobs, Desdemona; Bryant, John. Minority labor; Building Trades Council; Social Sciences Building; Stewart and Bennett, Inc.; Ithaca (NY) Southside Community Center; Ithaca-Cortland Builders Exchange Center; Southern Tier Area Negotiating Committee.
    - ROTC., 1969-70 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      Hittle, James D.; Brown, Stuart M. American Civil Liberties Union; Association of NROTC Colleges; Princeton University; University of California.
    - ROTC., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      Pusey, Nathan M.; Gladieux, Larry; Heberling, Earl J.; Kennedy, W. Keith; Orear, Jay; Kidd, Charles V. American Association of State Colleges and Universities; Association of American Universities.
    - ROTC. Gladieux, Larry; Kennedy, W. Keith; Guinn, D. H.; Storandt, Robert W.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Pusey, Nathan M. National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges; Association of NROTC Colleges; Association of American Universities; New York State Board of Regents., 1970-71 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - ROTC., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      Gladieux, Larry; Fitt, Alfred; Holm, Jeanne M. Association of American Universities.
    - ROTC., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      Williams, Robert L. Association of American Universities; United States Dept, of Defense; National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges.
    - Degree Programs for University Staff. Staff Degree Program; Committee on Educational Programs., 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Degree Programs for University Staff., 1968-71 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Hall, Jackson O.; Plane, Robert A.; Mover, Donald H.; Boissonnas, Christian; Leurgans, Paul J.; Gold, Charlotte. Staff Degree Program; Committee on Educational Programs.
    - Benefits., 1967-70 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Willers, Diedrich K. Group life insurance; Retirement Program.
    - Benefits., 1967-70 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Willers, Diedrich K. Health insurance; Unemployment insurance; TIAA-CREF.
    - Management Meeting, Second Echelon., 1968-70 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Rogers, Thomas R. Administrative Personnel Advisory Board; Professional Skills Roster.
    - Management Training Programs Committee. Huttar, James E.; Willers, Diedrich K.; Moyer, Donald H.; Risley, Robert F.; Leurgans, Paul J.; Peterson, Arthur H. New York State School, of Industrial and Labor Relations; Administrative positions., 1967-70 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Controller., 1967-70 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Peterson, Arthur H.; Brown, Stuart M.; Vogel, Jane; Nabokov, Vladimir. United States Post Office; Burns Detective Agency; Collective bargaining.
    - Office of the Controller., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Peterson, Arthur H. New York State Dormitory Authority.
    - Office of Institutional Studies., 1968-71 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Toomajian, Charles R.; Tetlow, William L.; Bowen, William G. Hill and Knowlton, Inc.
    - Accounting., 1965-68 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      Bates, J. E. Haskins and Sells, Inc.; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.
    - Auditing., 1966-69 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Peterson, Arthur H. McMullen Trust; Haskins and Sells.
    - Campus Store Advisory Committee., 1965-69 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Campus Store. Morse, Chandler; Krebs, Philip J.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Sokol, Thomas A.; Dowd, Douglas F.; Plane, Robert A. Alternate Book Store; Resistance Bookstore., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Director of Finance, State Units., 1967-69 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      Walsh, Robert L.
    - Real Estate., 1964-70 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Soyring, Andrew E. Peterson, Arthur H.; Patch, Roger. Llenroc.
    - Student Costs., 1970 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - University Printer., 1968-70 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      Arden, Kelvin J.; Miller, Robert D.; Kerns, M. R. University Messenger Service.
    - Director of the Budget., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      McKeegan, Paul L.; Clark, Van Alan.
    - Budget 1970-71., 1969 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Budget 1970-71., 1969-70 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Budget 1971-72., 1970 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Budget-Cutting Expenses., 1968-69 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      Kelly, Burnham.
    - Long Range Budget Study., 1968-69 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      Mackesey, Thomas W.
    - Cornell Plantations., 1964-71 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      Lewis, Richard M.; Howe, Holly L.; Wright, Theodore P. Cascadilla Gorge; Fall Creek Gorge; Sackett Gorge Fund.
    - Space Utilization and Assignment. Mackesey, Thomas W. Space needs; Facilities., 1967-71 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - University Apartments., 1968-69 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      Levis, J. Preston. Payson House.
    - Vice President for Public Affairs. Muller, Steven; Rossiter, Clinton; Mizener, Arthur M.; Winston, Oliver C. Winton G. Rossiter Scholarship; Inland Steel Company; Buckner Foundation; Becker Research Corporation; Public Affairs Workshop., 1969-70 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      Muller, Steven; Clynes, James. Rhodes Chair in Chemical Engineering; American Association of University Women; Goldwin Smith Hall.
    - Vice President for Public Affairs., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      Muller, Steven; Newman, Floyd R.; Levi, Julian H.; Lilienthal, Alfred; Purcell, Robert W.; Cornell, Robert G. Ithaca Festival of the Arts; Mohawk Airlines; American College Public Relations Association.
    - Alumni Affairs., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      Knight, John S.; McHugh, G. Michael; Todd, Walter L.; White, E. B.; Kaufman, Richard; Williams, L. Pearce; Snyder, Herb. Alumni Association; Cornell Alumni University.
    - Cornell Alumni News., 1968-71 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      Marcham, John; Hall, Jackson O. Alumni Association; Letters re May issue.
    - Cornell Alumni News., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      Meyer, Elmer E.; Marcham, John; Muller, Steven; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Purcell, Robert W. Africana Studies and Research Center; Matriculation fee; 1970 Commencement.
    - Class Reunions., 1970 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      Cornell Alumni Reunion Forum Program.
    - Cornell Alumni University., 1968-71 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      McHugh, G. Michael; Graham, Richard A.; Detmold, John H.
    - Committee on Memorials. Policies for naming new buildings., 1969-71 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Special Assistant for Community Relations., 1968-70 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      Kane, Robert J.; Muller, Steven; Mackesey, Thomas W. Community relations.
    - Community Relations., 1968-70 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      Sapakie, Alan L.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Hall, Jackson O.; Cook, Alice H.; Martin, Beverly J.; Lutz, Edward A.; Kane, Robert J. Community relations; Local taxes.
    - Community Relations. Hall, Jackson O.; Kane, Robert J.; Muller, Steven; Winston, Oliver C. Ithaca Southside Community Center; Community Relations Task Force; Community relations., 1970-71 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Community Relations., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      Saperstone, David A.; Shew, Randall E.; Barlow, Mark; Martin, Beverly J.; Muller, Steven; Kane, Robert J. Director of Community Relations; Community relations.
    - Cornell Chronicle., 1969-71 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      Tobin, Thomas L.; Hilton, Peter J.; Plane, Robert A.; Starobin, Robert; Cook, Alice H.; Whitlock, John H.
    - Public Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Cornell Fund., 1966-70 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Uris, Harold D. United Fund.
    - Cornell University - New York City. Eager, George B.; Straton, Sally S. Center for Educational Enquiry; Television; James A. Perkins' The University in Transition., 1965-69 (Box 37, Folder 2)